(Mrs Cooper:)What do we do
when someone's hurting?
(Sheldon:)Offer them a hot beverage.
(Mrs Cooper:)When they're drunk as a skunk,
what beverage do we offer?
(Sheldon:)Coffee.
(Mrs Cooper:)And what do we do it with?
(Mrs Cooper:)Now, you listen to me.
(Mrs Cooper:)I know you feel
Iike you can't find someone...
(Mrs Cooper:)...but there's a lock for every key.
(Mrs Cooper:)Back home, there's a girl works
at the Walmart. Tall, tall girI.
(Mrs Cooper:)Woman could hunt geese with a rake.
(Mrs Cooper:)Thought she'd never find a man,
then one day, wouldn't you know...
(Mrs Cooper:)...Harlem Globetrotters come to town.
(Mrs Cooper:)Long story short,
today that woman travels the world...
(Mrs Cooper:)...with a semiprofessional
basketball player...
(Mrs Cooper:)...and two beautiful
mixed-race babies.
(Raj:)I didn't get a lot of that
because of your accent...
(Raj:)...but the general tone was soothing
and somehow I feel better. Ha, ha.